Guide to the Connecticut Regional Medical Program Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- CORRESPONDENCE FILES, 1965-1976; Series VIII; 24' (21 boxes)
  - General Correspondence
    - Evans, Lester (Box 31)
    - Fabro, J. Alfred (Box 31)
    - Fenniger, Leonard (Bureau of Health Manpower) (Box 31)
    - Hamilton, T. Stewart (Box 31)
    - Health Services Research Center (Box 31)
    - Hiscock, Ira V. (Box 31)
    - Hunter, Gertrude (Box 31)
    - Joint Commission on Accreditation of Hospitals (Box 31)
    - Kissick, William (Box 31)
    - Kunkel, Paul (Box 31)
    - Lippard Document (Box 31)
    - Lisansky, Milton (Box 31)
    - MacLeod, Gordon K. (Box 31)
    - McMahon, John A. (Box 31)
    - Matching funds list (Box 31)
    - Mayors, Connecticut Conference of, 1974 September (Box 31)
    - Medical education in Connecticut hospitals (Box 31)
    - Meetings attended 1968-1972, correspondence re: (Box 31)
    - Meetings attended, 1973-1974, correspondence re: (Box 32)
    - Minority information, RMP's analysis (Box 32)
    - Model Cities (Box 32)
    - Neumann, Hans H. (Box 32)
    - New England Regional Medical Planning Commission (Box 32)
    - New England Regional Medical Planning Foundation (Box 32)
    - New Haven County Medical Association (Box 32)
    - Newhallville, United Organization of Northeast Regional Medical Program Coordinators Meetings, 1967-1976 (Box 32)
    - Norwood, George M., Jr. (Box 33)
    - Nursing data (Box 33)
    - Nursing, general information re: meetings on Overview statements (Box 33)
    - Planning agencies in Connecticut (Box 33)
    - Professional Activity Study (Box 33)
    - Program coordinators, RMPs in U.S. (Box 33)
    - Public Laws 89-239, 89-749, 91-515 (Box 33)
    - Quinnipiac College, program in Health Services Administration (Box 33)
    - Regional Medical Program (RMP) California (Box 33)
    - Regional Medical Program (RMP) Central New York (Box 33)
    - Regional Medical Program (RMP) Lakes Area (Buffalo, N.Y.) (Box 33)
    - Regional Medical Program (RMP) Maine (Box 33)
    - Regional Medical Program (RMP) Metropolitan New York (Box 33)
    - Regional Medical Program (RMP) Tri-State (Massachusetts, New Hampshire, Rhode Island) (Box 33)
    - Regional Medical Program Liaison-Boston, HEW (Box 33)
    - Relevance documents re: Yale-New Haven Health Center Reports, requests for (Box 33)
    - Rhode Island Health Science Education Council (Box 33)
    - Rogers, Arthur (Chairman CRMP Advisory Board) (Box 33)
    - Schaffer Committee on Hospital Costs (Box 33)
    - Sklaver-Della Pietra letter re: St. Mary's and Waterbury Hospital affiliations (Box 33)
    - Snoke, Albert W. (Box 33)
    - Spring, William C., Jr. (Box 33)
    - Stiles, George (Box 33)
    - TB and Respiratory Disease Association (Box 33)
    - United Way of Connecticut (Box 33)
  - University of Connecticut
    - Department of Community Medicine (Box 33)
    - Elling, Ray (Box 33)
    - General Correspondence (Box 33)
    - Glasgow, John (Box 34)
    - Massey, Robert U. (Box 34)
    - Patterson, John (Dean, University of Connecticut School of Medicine) (Box 34)
  - Yale University School of Medicine
    - Berliner, Robert (Box 34)
    - Board of Permanent Officers (Box 34)
    - Clinical Consultation Services (Box 34)
    - Cohart, Edward (Box 34)
    - Cole, Jack (Box 34)
    - Council on Medical Services (Box 34)
    - Epidemiology and Public Health (Box 34)
    - Fetter, Robert B. (Box 34)
    - Conferences on Medical School and Community-Hospital Relations (Box 34)
    - Kligerman, Morton M. (Box 34)
    - Korper, Samuel P. (Box 34)
    - Lawton, Robert P. (Box 34)
    - McCollum, Robert (Box 34)
    - Medical Board, Yale-New Haven Hospital (Box 34)
    - Medical Development Committee (Box 34)
    - Ostfeld, Adrian (Box 34)
    - Pearson, David (Box 34)
    - Pearson, R. John C. (Box 34)
    - Pellegrino, Edward (Box 34)
    - Redlick, Frederick (Box 34)
    - Reidel, Donald (Box 34)
    - Sheig, Robert (Box 34)
    - Southwick, Wayne (Box 34)
    - Student evaluations (Box 34)
    - Thomas, Lewis (Box 34)
    - Thompson, John (Box 34)
    - Weinerman, E. Richard (Box 34)
    - Welt, Louis (Box 34)
    - Womer, Charles (Box 34)
  - Outgoing Daily Correspondence
    - Outgoing daily correspondence, 1967-1976 (Box 34)
      - Correspondence with individual state hospitals 1966-1975 A-G (Box 35)
    - Correspondence with individual state hospitals 1966-1975 H-Z (Box 36)
  - Ongoing CRMP Programs
    - Yale University
      - Community Studies Unit (Box 37)
      - Office of Regional Activities (Box 37)
      - Impact of full-time chiefs' study (Box 37)
      - Coordination Committee for CRMP (Box 37)
      - Colloquium Planning Committee (Box 37)
      - Gastroenterology Program (Box 37)
      - Diabetes Teaching and Consultation Program (Box 37)
    - University of Connecticut
      - Community Studies Unit (Box 37)
      - Regional faculty, dental (Box 37)
      - Regional faculty, nursing (Box 37)
      - School of Allied Health Professions (Box 37)
    - Emergency Medical Services (Box 38)
    - Physician's Assistant Program (Box 38)
    - Association of Community Health Service Agencies (Box 38)
    - Bridgeport Pediatric Continuing Care Program (Box 38)
    - New Britain Comprehensive Child Health Program (Box 38)
    - Waterbury Regional Pediatric Program (Box 38)
    - Hartford Hospital Primary Care Center (Box 39)
    - Yale-New Haven Primary Care Nursing Training (Box 39)
    - Hill Health Center (Box 39)
    - Community Care Plan (Box 39)
    - Connecticut Network for Medical Communications (Box 39)
    - Coronary Care (Box 39)
    - Stroke Program Committee (Box 40)
    - Special Services Radiation (Box 40)
    - Waterbury Computer Capability Survey (Box 40)
    - Arthritis Program (Box 41)
    - Southern Connecticut Regional Health Education Program (Box 41)
    - University-Community Hospital Partnerships (Box 41)
    - Regional Hospice Development Program (Box 41)
    - Connecticut Health Services Research Series (Box 41)
    - Connecticut Hospital Pediatric Study for Connecticut (Box 41)
    - New Haven Ambulatory Care Project (Box 41)
    - Library Services Project (Box 41)
    - Library Services Newsletter (Box 42)
    - Southern Connecticut Continuing Care Demonstration (Box 42)
    - Health Service Area Planning Assistance (Box 42)
    - Regional Blood Bank Program (Box 42)
    - Neighborhood Health Services (Box 42)
    - Allied Health Manpower Development (Box 42)
    - New Haven Institute of Allied Health Carriers (Box 42)
    - Medical Center Committee on Education of Allied Health Personnel (Box 42)
    - Connecticut Drug Information Service (Box 42)
    - Personnel Health Services Planning (Box 42)
  - Department of Health, Education and Welfare
    - England, Joseph (Box 42)
    - Richardson, Elliot (Box 42)
  - National Institutes of Health
    - Clinical Center (Box 42)
    - Marston, Robert Q. (Director, NIH) (Box 42)
    - National Advisory Council Meeting, 1975 June (Box 42)
  - Regional Medical Programs Service and other RMPs
    - General Correspondence, 1966-1973 (Box 42)
    - Public information data (Box 42)
    - Lewis, Gregory (Box 42)
    - Endicott, Kenneth (Box 42)
    - Management survey meeting (Box 42)
    - Pahl, Herbert (Box 42)
    - Margulies, Harold (Director, RMPS) (Box 43)
    - Faatz, Eileen (Box 43)
    - Peterson, Roland (Box 43)
    - Pasta, Mike (Box 43)
    - Sibsbee, Sarah (Box 43)
    - Wilson, Vernon (Box 43)
    - Conferences, 1968-1972 (Box 43)
    - Maine RMP (Box 44)
    - Lakes Area RMP (Box 44)
    - Tri-State RMP (Box 44)
  - State of Connecticut: Miscellaneous Offices and Agencies
    - Governor's Office (Ella Grasso) (Box 44)
      See also: box 45
    - Filer Committee on the Structure of State Government (Box 44)
    - Department of Financing and Control (Box 44)
    - Commission on Hospitals and Health Care (Box 44)
    - State Department of Health (Box 44)
    - State Department of Mental Health (Box 44)
    - Director of Health Associates (Box 44)
    - State Department of Welfare (Box 44)
    - Department of Aging (Box 44)
    - Title XX Social Security (Box 44)
    - CIDS (Coordinated Information and Data System, State Health Department) (Box 44)
    - CIDS (cont'd) (Box 45)
    - Radiation Centers in Connecticut (Box 45)
    - Nursing Homes in Connecticut (Box 45)
    - State Public Health and Safety Committee (Box 45)
    - Patterson Committee (Regional Health Resources Commission) (Box 45)
  - State of Connecticut Congressional Delegation
    - Cotter, William R. (Box 45)
    - Dodd, Christopher J. (Box 45)
    - Giamo, Robert N. (Box 45)
    - Grasso, Ella T. (Box 45)
    - McKinney, Stewart B. (Box 45)
    - Moffet, Toby (Box 45)
    - Ribicoff, Abraham (Box 45)
    - Sarasin, Ronald A. (Box 45)
    - Steele, Robert M (Box 45)
    - Weicker, Lowell, Jr. (Box 45)
  - State of Connecticut Council on Human Services
    - A-95 Review Process Correspondence, 1971-1974 (Box 45)
    - Correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box 46)
  - Connecticut State Medical Society
    - Correspondence, 1968 (Box 46)
    - Correspondence, 1968-1974 (Box 47)
    - Compendium of CSMS-CRMP Relationships, 1967-1975 (Box 47)
  - State of Connecticut Health Service Areas(HSAs)
    - HSA I (Box 47)
    - HSA II (Box 48)
    - HSA III (Box 48)
    - HSA IV (Box 48)
    - HSA V (Box 48)
  - Connecticut Citizen Research Group
    - Consumer education (Box 48)
    - Monthly reports, 1975-1976 (Box 48)
  - State of Connecticut Comprehensive Health Planning Agencies(CHPs)
    - Comprehensive Health Planning Agencies: mailing list, 1972 (Box 48)
    - Regional orientation sessions on health resources planning, 1975 January (Box 48)
    - American Association for Comprehensive Health Planning (Box 48)
    - Comprehensive Health planning "A" Agency (Box 48)
    - Comprehensive Health Planning "B" Agency (Box 48)
    - New Haven-South Central CHP (Box 48)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1972 (Box 48)
    - Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 49)
    - CHP planning, 1968-1970 (Box 49)
  - Miscellaneous Research Groups and Service Organizations
    - Friends of RMP (Box 49)
    - Inter-Regional Representative, RMP (Box 49)
    - Urban League (National and Greater Hartford) (Box 50)
    - New Haven Health Care, Inc. (Box 50)
    - Commission on Primary Care (Box 50)
    - National Cancer Institute (Box 50)
    - National Association of RMPs, Inc. (Box 50)